<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Motor-Bike Care</string>
    <string name="MAPS_API_KEY">AIzaSyDalSgFJjk9q06ftHJzbgUmD_da66s4Iak</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="nav_graph_destination_id_user_home">userHome</string>
    <string name="nav_graph_destination_id_user_order_history">userOrderHistory</string>
    <string name="nav_graph_destination_id_user_profile">userProfile</string>
    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
    <string name="contributors_heading">Contributors</string>
    <string name="theme_app_heading">Theme</string>
    <string name="about_us_heading">About Us</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_heading">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="rate_us_heading">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="share_app_heading">Share App</string>
    <string name="logout_auth_heading">Logout</string>
    <string name="exit_app_heading">Exit!</string>
    <string name="map_output_1">cv|5MD389t[+ $0.5</string>
    <string name="map_output_2">sdk not installed, basic package!</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy" formatted="true">
        <b>Saturday, 26 August 2023</b>
        \n\nThank you for choosing SmartBike, a mobile application. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you use the SmartBike app. By using the App, you consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
        <b>\n\nInformation We Collect</b>
        <b>\n\nLocation Data:</b>
        \nWe request access to your device\'s location to offer features such as route tracking, navigation, and personalized biking recommendations. Your location data is collected only with your explicit consent and is used solely within the App to enhance your biking experience.
        <b>\n\nMedia/Images:</b>
        \nThe App may request access to your device\'s media/images to enable you to upload and share images related to your biking activities. You have the option to provide or deny this permission. Any images you choose to share are used within the App for personalization and community interaction.
        <b>\n\nData Security</b>
        \n\nWe take the security of your data seriously and implement reasonable measures to protect it from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that no method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is entirely secure.
        <b>\n\nThird-Party Services</b>
        \n\nWe may utilize third-party services, such as mapping and location services, to improve the functionality of the App. These services have their own privacy policies and terms of use. We recommend reviewing these policies before using the App.
        <b>\n\nContact Us</b>
        \n\nIf you have any questions, concerns, or inquiries about this Privacy Policy or your interactions with the App, please contact us.
        <b>\n\nEffective Date</b>
        \n\nThis Privacy Policy was last updated on Saturday, 26 August 2023.
    </string>

    <string name="about_us" formatted="true">
        Welcome to SmartBike, your ultimate companion for an enhanced biking experience!
        \n\nAt SmartBike, we are passionate about cycling and technology, and we\'ve combined these two passions to create an app that revolutionizes the way you ride. Whether you\'re a casual rider, a dedicated cyclist, or someone looking to explore your city on two wheels, SmartBike is designed with you in mind.
        <b>\n\nOur Mission</b>
        \n\nOur mission is to empower bikers of all levels by providing them with innovative tools and features that make biking more enjoyable, interactive, and rewarding. We believe that cycling isn\'t just a mode of transportation it\'s a lifestyle, a source of joy, and a means to connect with others. Through SmartBike, we aim to enhance these aspects of biking while also promoting a healthy and sustainable way of getting around.
        <b>\n\nKey Features</b>
        <b>\n\n\u25CF Route Tracking:</b> Use SmartBike to track your routes, monitor your progress, and analyze your biking performance. Our GPS-enabled tracking system ensures that you never miss a beat.
        <b>\n\n\u25CF Navigation:</b> Say goodbye to getting lost! SmartBike offers intuitive navigation that guides you along the best biking routes, helping you discover new paths and explore your surroundings.
        <b>\n\n\u25CF Community:</b> Connect with a community of fellow bikers who share your passion. Share your biking experiences, photos, and achievements, and engage in discussions to stay inspired.
        <b>\n\n\u25CF Personalization:</b> Customize your profile with photos and details that showcase your biking personality. Let your profile reflect your unique journey as a cyclist.
        <b>\n\n\u25CF Local Insights:</b> Unlock local biking insights and recommendations. Find the best cycling trails, pit stops, and bike-friendly establishments in your area.
        <b>\n\nGet in Touch</b>
        \n\nWe value your feedback and input as we strive to make SmartBike the ultimate biking companion. If you have any questions, suggestions, or ideas, don\'t hesitate to reach out to us. Your input helps us shape the future of SmartBike and ensures that the app continues to meet the needs of the cycling community.
        \n\nHappy riding!
        \n\nThe SmartBike Team
    </string>

    <string name="contributors">
        Heartfelt gratitude to Ashir and Hamza for their invaluable contributions to the SmartBike application. Your dedication, and expertise have played a significant role in shaping the app into what it is today.
    </string>

    <string name="rate_us">
        Enjoying your SmartBike experience? We\'d love to hear your thoughts! If you\'re finding our app helpful and enjoyable on your cycling adventures, consider taking a moment to rate us.
    </string>

    <string name="theme_app">
        SmartBike\'s sleek and intuitive Android application theme seamlessly blends style and functionality. Designed with cyclists in mind, our theme enhances your biking experience.
    </string>

    <string name="share_app">
        Spread the joy of biking with SmartBike! If you\'re having a blast exploring new routes and tracking your rides, why not share the excitement? Invite your fellow cyclists and friends to join the SmartBike community.
    </string>

    <string name="thank_you">
        We wanted to take a moment to express our heartfelt gratitude for choosing SmartBike for your recent purchase. We\'re thrilled to have you as part of our biking community.
    </string>

    <string name="close_application">
        Oh no! You\'re leaving Are you sure? 🥺
    </string>

    <array name="auth_role_menu">
        <item>user</item>
        <item>mechanic</item>
    </array>

    <array name="product_category_menu">
        <item>Engine</item>
        <item>Engine oil</item>
        <item>Engine parts</item>
        <item>Lights</item>
        <item>Tires</item>
    </array>

    <array name="service_category_menu">
        <item>Engine service</item>
        <item>Engine oil change</item>
        <item>Engine repair</item>
        <item>Brake service</item>
        <item>Tire puncture</item>
        <item>Washing</item>
        <item>Decoration</item>
    </array>

</resources>